go go go go let's go sh it
上上上上上上上上上上上上上上
going the dangerous
危险飞行中
calls
调来电话
wow oh look it's a
哇哦,看啊,这是一个
UFO
哇,看啊,这是UFO
UFO 乌弗果
UFO
my ice
我的冰冰
cream fugitive brown bear call the
奶油散逸的棕熊呼叫
police immediately if you see him
奶油 逃逃的棕熊 见到他立刻报警
见到他立即报警
police immediately if you see him
H
见到H就立即报警
赫 时
H
hey woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 我是拉布拉多警长
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长
hey woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador I saw brown bear The Fugitive
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 我看到棕熊
拉布拉多 我看到棕熊"逃犯"
Labrador I saw brown bear The Fugitive
what where is he now he's hiding at 10
拉布拉多,我看见棕熊棕熊 《逃犯》 他现在在哪里 他躲在10点
他现在在哪里? 他躲在10点
what where is he now he's hiding at 10
Rose Road protect yourself and stay safe
他现在在哪里 他躲在10号玫瑰路 保护自己和保持安全
玫瑰路保护自己 并保持安全
Rose Road protect yourself and stay safe
we'll be right
玫瑰之路保护自己 并保持安全 我们会是正确的
我们就会是对的
we'll be right
there huh
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈;
huh it's full of dust here and there
到處都是灰尘
aren't any
这里到处都是灰尘 没有
没有
aren't any
Footprints this place has been
这里没有脚印
此地方的脚印
Footprints this place has been
unoccupied for a very long time would it
这个地方的脚印已经被占用了很长一段时间 如果可以的话
长期无人居住,如果它
unoccupied for a very long time would it
be
长期无人居住,如果是
that Sher Labrador brown bear is coming
谢尔拉布拉多棕熊来了
after me I'm hiding right by the
谢尔拉布拉多棕熊要来追我 我就躲在
beehives
蜜蜂
H found
找到 H 发现
youoh it's not brown bear it's Mr Black
不是棕熊,不是黑熊,是黑先生
Bear is there something wrong
不是棕熊 是黑熊先生出事了
熊熊有什么不对劲吗?
Bear is there something wrong
officer I am just here to buy some
大熊有问题吗? 警官,我只是来买
警官,我只是来买一些
officer I am just here to buy some
honey it's so much fun I'm going to call
蜂蜜,它是如此的乐趣 我要打电话给
the police again and lie about brown
亲爱的,这太有趣了 我要再次报警 并撒谎关于棕色
Bear Brown
贝尔布朗
Bear H looking at the two prank calls
熊H看着两个恶作剧电话
I'm sure little fox did them just for
熊 H 看着两个恶作剧电话 我敢肯定小狐狸只为了
我敢肯定小狐狸只为
I'm sure little fox did them just for
fun what little fox prank
我敢肯定小狐狸做它们只是为了取乐 什么小狐狸恶作剧
什么小狐狸恶作剧
fun what little fox prank
calls
有趣的小狐狸恶作剧
oh help me sure
哦,帮我确定
labador kidnapped me
帮我确定拉巴多绑架了我
Labador绑架我
labador kidnapped me
liar you're lying again please help me
拉巴多绑架我骗骗我 你又在撒谎 请帮帮我
你骗骗我,你又在说谎了 请你帮帮我
liar you're lying again please help me
this is not a lie don't you know that
你骗人,你又在撒谎 请帮帮我 这不是谎言,你不知道吗?
这不是谎言,你不知道吗?
this is not a lie don't you know that
making false police calls is against the
这不是谎言,你不知道 做假警察的呼唤是反对的
造假的警察来电是反对的
making false police calls is against the
law no I think little fox isn't
做假警察报警是违法的 我想小狐狸不是
没有法律,我觉得小狐狸不是
law no I think little fox isn't
lying listen to The Echoes and the sound
我想小狐狸不是在撒谎 听回声和声音
说谎 听回音 听回音
lying listen to The Echoes and the sound
of the engine he might be trapped in a
听回音和引擎的声音 他可能被困在
引擎的引擎,他可能 被困在
of the engine he might be trapped in a
car right
他可能被困在一辆汽车里
now brown bear I'm brown bear every body
现在,棕熊,我棕熊 每个身体,我都是棕熊
scare of me
棕熊,现在我变成棕熊 全身都害怕我
怕我怕我
scare of me
yeah follow
吓吓我,吓吓我,吓吓我,吓吓我,吓我吓吓我,吓我吓吓我,吓我怕我吓怕,吓我怕我吓吓我,吓我怕我怕我,吓我怕我怕我,吓我怕我怕我,吓我怕我怕我,吓我怕我,吓我怕我,吓我怕,吓我怕我,吓我怕我,吓我怕,吓我怕,吓我怕,吓我怕,吓我怕,吓怕我
续 续
yeah follow
him brown bear stop the car stop the car
棕熊 车停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停
now huh
棕熊把车停了,快停车
police they're so annoying let me show
警察很烦人,让我看看
you what I can
警察很烦人 让我给你看看我有什么能耐
do ow ow ow
哟哟啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
oh no they're right behind
他们就在后面
me ah I need to
我啊,我需要,我需要
run stop right
我啊,我需要跑 停下来右转停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停
运行停止右右
run stop right
there huh you can't run away from us I
你逃不掉我们
was so
你逃不掉我们,我当时...
确实如此
was so
scared it's okay you're safe now but
害怕得要命 你现在安全了,没事的,但是...
害怕你现在安全了,但...
scared it's okay you're safe now but
remember you shouldn't make false police
怕你现在安全了,没事的 记得不要当假警察
记得你不该做假警察
remember you shouldn't make false police
calls for fun I I'm so
记得你不该用假警察的电话 来找乐子吗?
sorry sheriff labrador's safety
对不起 警长拉布拉多的安全
talk making false police calls are
对不起 警长拉布拉多的安全谈话 做假警察的电话是
胡言乱语 做假警察电话是
talk making false police calls are
against the law it leads police to wrong
说假的报警电话是违法的 导致警察误入歧途
违反法律,导致警察犯错
against the law it leads police to wrong
places so people in need can't get
违法 导致警察去错地方 让有需要的人得不到
让有需要的人得不到
places so people in need can't get
help kids please call the police only
让有需要的人得不到帮助 孩子们请只报警
帮助孩子,请只报警
help kids please call the police only
when you're actually in danger never
帮助孩子,请在有危险时才报警
当你实际上处于危险中时 永远不会
when you're actually in danger never
make false police calls just for
当你身处险境时 永远不要打假警察的电话
凭空造假警用假警用电话
make false police calls just for
fun don't put your head between the
别把你的头放在中间
别把头放在中间
fun don't put your head between the
fence wo come on
别把你的头放在栅栏之间 来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去
来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊
fence wo come on
Daddy ice cream ice cream all right wait
来,爸爸冰淇淋冰淇淋冰淇淋
爸爸冰淇淋冰淇淋冰淇淇淋 所有的权利等待等待
Daddy ice cream ice cream all right wait
here until I come back
爸爸冰淇淋冰淇淋 冰淇淋很好 在这里等我回来
uh-huh it's a little train let's go take
嗯,这是一个小火车,我们去走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走
a
嗯,这是一个小火车 让我们去走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走
look wo
看,看,看,看,看,看,看
it's so
就是这样
pretty My Head Is
美丽的我的头
Stuck mine
我漂亮的头,我的头发,是 斯塔克矿井
堆积地雷
Stuck mine
too
也一样
no kidss where are you
没有孩子,你在哪里?
kids Mr donkey what's going on my kids
没有孩子,你在哪里 孩子们在哪里,你的孩子 驴先生 什么是怎么回事 我的孩子们
蠢驴先生 我的孩子出了什么事
kids Mr donkey what's going on my kids
are missing they were here a few minutes
驴小子先生,我孩子失踪了 他们在这里呆了几分钟
失踪了,他们在这里呆了几分钟
are missing they were here a few minutes
ago don't worry let's look around
他们失踪了 他们几分钟前就在这里了 别担心 我们四处看看吧
here oh I found their
我在这里找到了他们的
Footprints and the footprints stop right
脚印和脚印停在右侧
here h
脚印和脚印停在这里
the fence is
栅栏是
missing huh it looks like someone
栅栏不见了啊 看起来像某人
似乎有人失踪了
missing huh it looks like someone
dragged it the fence marks and the
似乎有人拖着它 栅栏标志和
挂着栅栏的标志和
dragged it the fence marks and the
donkey's Footprints go all the way to
和驴的脚印 一路走到
驴的脚印 一路跑到
donkey's Footprints go all the way to
the track and
驴脚印一直跑到赛道上
轨道和
the track and
disappear
和消失的轨道
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
huh oh no they're stuck in the
哦,不,他们被卡在
train let's
火车,让我们
go
火车,我们走吧
help somebody
帮助帮助某人
help watch
帮助帮助帮助看者
me
我,我,我
huh oh no it's going into the tunnel huh
不对,要进隧道了,哈哈哈哈哈哈
哦,不,它进入隧道了,呵呵
huh oh no it's going into the tunnel huh
that's it hold tight let's
哦,不,它要进入隧道了 嗯,它保持紧紧,让我们
go
上去
wow the Dino's
哇,迪诺的
flying
哇 迪诺在飞
hey watch
嘿,看,嘿,看
out we're getting
嘿,小心我们得到
out a
外部a
h get the
h 得到
fence let's go hey what a bad
栅栏,让我们去嘿嘿,多么糟糕
day
天天
huh it's
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF
stuck over there
被困在那边
hurry don't worry we'll get you
不用担心,快点,别担心 我们会抓到你的
out
外出
come on
出来 出来 出来
Toby it was so scary we will never do
托比 我们永远也做不来 托比太吓人了
that
托比太吓人了 我们绝对不会那样做的
,该数额,
that
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids don't put your head between
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们不要把你的头放在中间
说闲话的小孩不要把你的头放在
talk kids don't put your head between
fences for fun or out of
说闲话的小孩 不要把你的头放在栅栏之间 玩玩或玩不玩
用于娱乐或娱乐的栅栏
fences for fun or out of
curiosity it's very dangerous because
为了取乐或好奇的乐趣或出于好奇的围栅非常危险,因为
好奇心很危险,因为
curiosity it's very dangerous because
you could get stuck and hurt yourself if
好奇心很危险 因为你可能会被卡住 伤到自己
你可能会被卡住 伤害自己,如果
you could get stuck and hurt yourself if
you're stuck don't try to figure it out
如果你被卡住了,你可能会被卡住 受伤自己 如果你被卡住,不要试图找出来
你被卡住了,别想弄清楚
you're stuck don't try to figure it out
by yourself ask adults for
你被困了,别想自己去想 自己去问大人要什么
自己一个人去问成年人
by yourself ask adults for
help please remember
帮助您记住
that super
超级
capeman keeping the forest safe for
那个超级斗牛人 保持森林安全
保护森林安全
capeman keeping the forest safe for
Justice's
为正义的护林者 保持森林安全
司法正义
Justice's
sake I'm super
看在正义的份上,我超棒
我超棒,我超棒
sake I'm super
ceman haha ha wow you're
看在上帝的份上,我是超级 塞满哈哈哈哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇
采曼哈哈哈哇哇哇你
ceman haha ha wow you're
awesome attention all citizens there's a
切曼哈哈哈 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 哇哇 你非常受关注 全体市民
全体市民注意,这里有一个
awesome attention all citizens there's a
burglar going around digging tunnels and
全体市民注意 有个盗贼到处在挖隧道
盗贼到处挖隧道
burglar going around digging tunnels and
stealing things if you find any clues
盗贼到处挖隧道 偷东西 如果你找到任何线索
如果你发现什么线索,就偷东西;
stealing things if you find any clues
about the suspect please contact us it's
如果你找到嫌犯的线索 就会偷东西 请联系我们
疑疑嫌疑人 请联系我们 这是
about the suspect please contact us it's
so scary don't worry I'll keep the bad
疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑嫌犯疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑疑
怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕,怕怕怕怕怕怕
so scary don't worry I'll keep the bad
guy away with my cap
这么吓人,不用担心,我会不让坏人 带着我的帽子离开我的帽子
attack
攻击攻击
huh nobody's here this is my
这儿没人,这是我的
chance the sple from
机会的溢出,
TV here's my cack
电视机的弹孔,这是我的垃圾
电视,这是我的垃圾
TV here's my cack
woohoo
呼呼呼呼呼呼
hey
嘿
see even the burglar scared of me stop
连偷贼都怕我
right
连那个偷盗贼都怕我,你给我站住
右右右右右
right
there wait
在那里等待,等待,等待,等待
stop wo hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador the tunnel digging burglar is
停下 嗨 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多隧道挖掘窃贼
拉布拉多 隧道挖盗贼
Labrador the tunnel digging burglar is
here what we'll be right
拉布拉多 隧道挖土贼在这里 我们会做对的事
there
此处
Sheriff lador my brother went after the
警长长长,我哥哥去追
burlar what he might be in
警长长长,我哥哥去追斗篷... ...他可能身在何地
Danger let's go find him
危险,我们去找他
now
现在
hurry
快点
ouch
触摸( A)
stop right
# 右停右停 #
there
此处
help I got
在那里帮助我得到
帮助我得到了
help I got
you
帮助我找到你
您 您 的 您 您
you
ouch ow let me go please I'll give you
你让我走,求你了,我给你
让我走吧,求你了,我给你
ouch ow let me go please I'll give you
all of my treasure here take it
让我走吧,求你了,我把我的财宝都给你,拿去吧
all Super K man defeated the tunnel
超级K人打败了隧道
digging burglar
超级K人击败了挖土贼的隧道
挖土贼
digging burglar
huh oh my it's just a
挖窃贼啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
哦,我的哦,它只是一个
huh oh my it's just a
kid I'm super geman keep prot
小子,我是超级宝石 保持普罗特
attack keep
继续攻击
attack you dare try to trick
攻击,你敢想耍花招
me Sher Le
舍尔勒
it's okay you're safe
舍勒,没事的,你安全了
没关系,你安全了
it's okay you're safe
now
现在
stop stop right
现在停停停右停停停停停停停停
there
此处
stop hey stop right
站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住,站住
there ah it's a dead end you have
在那里啊,这是一个死胡同 你有一个
nowhere to run oh
那儿啊 死胡同 你无处可逃啊
无处可逃哦
nowhere to run oh
no
无处无处可逃
aha
aha (公顷)
dig dig dig you'll never catch
挖挖挖,你永远抓不到
me so
所以,我如此
H
赫 时
stop d
停止 d
d
d , d , d , d , d , d , d , d , d , d , d
oh no he got
哦,不,他得到了
away watch
离开观察
me oh man he's so
哦,伙计,他是如此
sneaky huh I have an
哦,伙计,他这么鬼鬼鬼祟祟,我有一个
idea don't be stink
思想不要发臭
bomb you think you can catch me no
炸弹,你认为你能抓住我? 不
way what's that
炸弹,你认为你可以抓不到我
smell
气味气味
it
其 其 年 , 其 年 , 其 年 , 其
stinks nobody can run away from
臭臭,没人能逃避
me Sheriff labrador's safety
我是拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids if you run across bad guys
如果你遇到坏人,就跟小孩说闲话
don't panic and don't try to show off
如果你碰到坏人,就跟小孩说闲话 不要惊慌,不要炫耀
不要惊慌,不要炫耀
don't panic and don't try to show off
and be a hero never try to fight
不要惊慌,不要炫耀 做一个英雄,永远不要打架
成为英雄 永远不试图战斗
and be a hero never try to fight
them stay calm and stay away from them
做一个英雄 永远不要试图和他们战斗 保持冷静 远离他们
他们保持冷静,远离他们,
them stay calm and stay away from them
and ask for help from your parents or a
他们保持冷静,远离他们,向父母或父母寻求帮助。
且向父母或父母求援,
and ask for help from your parents or a
police
且向父母或警察求助,
警 警 警 警察
police
officer please keep that in
军官,请保留在
mind don't open the door to
警官,请记住,不要开门到
strangers right there
陌生人就在那里
wol oh no huh
呵呵不呵呵呵呵呵呵呵呵呵呵呵呵
wow
哇哇哇哇
thanks where did he
哇,多谢了,他在哪里
go that was close I need to find a place
差得近,我需要找个地方
to
我需要找个地方
hide mommy will be back soon okay and
藏起来的妈妈很快会回来的,好吗?
remember never open the door to
妈妈很快就会回来 记住永远不要开门
记住永远不要打开大门
remember never open the door to
strangers don't worry I won't bye-bye
记住永远不要向陌生人敞开大门 不要担心 我不会再见的
陌生人不用担心,我不会再见的
strangers don't worry I won't bye-bye
mommy
陌生人不用担心 我不会再见妈妈的
妈妈
mommy
bye great little rabbit is home all
妈妈再见,大小兔子都在家
再见 小小兔子全家在家
bye great little rabbit is home all
alone this is my
再见,小兔兔在家 独自一人,这是我的
chance who is
何人的机会
it hello little kid I'm a delivery man I
我是一个送货员
你好,小小孩,我是送货员
it hello little kid I'm a delivery man I
have a package for you a package please
你好,小孩子,我是送货员 我有一个包裹给你,请给我一个包裹
请为您提供包裹包,请为您提供包裹包
have a package for you a package please
open the door and sign here leave it at
有个包裹包给你 一个包裹包 请打开门签字
打开门,在这里签字,留下
open the door and sign here leave it at
the door
打开门,在这里签字 放在门前
门门
the door
please come on look at this there are
门,请来,看看这个,这里有
请你过来看看这个,这里有
please come on look at this there are
lots of yummy
来,来,来,看看这个 有很多好吃的
大量美味
lots of yummy
snacks chocolates lollipops jellies and
很多好吃的零食巧克力棒棒糖果冻和
零食巧克力棒棒糖果冻
snacks chocolates lollipops jellies and
chips wow they look so yummy oh yeah
巧克力小点心棒棒棒糖和薯片 哇,它们看起来好好吃哦耶
薯片哇哇,他们看起来好好吃哦耶
chips wow they look so yummy oh yeah
your mommy has bought all of these for
薯片看起来好好吃哦 你妈妈买了这些
这些都是你妈妈买给你的
your mommy has bought all of these for
you now please open the
你妈妈给你买了所有这些 现在请打开
door remember never open the door to
永远不要把门打开到
strangers right I shouldn't open the
记住大门永远不要打开 陌生人的门 我不应该打开
陌生人的权利 我不应该打开
strangers right I shouldn't open the
door I need to wait until mommy's
陌生人,我不应该打开门 我需要等到妈妈的
我要等到妈妈的门
door I need to wait until mommy's
back she's not
我要等到妈妈回来,她才回来
背着她不是
back she's not
fooled H let me
回来后她又没被骗过 让我来
被骗的H 让我来
fooled H let me
think ha that's
被骗的H 让我想想哈哈
it who is it it's Mommy open the door
是谁啊? 是妈妈开门
Mommy
是谁啊? 是妈妈开门,妈妈
妈咪妈妈妈妈
Mommy
H but your voice sounds a little strange
妈妈H,但你的声音 听起来有点奇怪
H,但你的声音 听起来有点奇怪
H but your voice sounds a little strange
mommy oh that's because I've got cold
但你的声音听起来有点奇怪 妈妈哦,那是因为我感冒了
妈妈哦,那是因为我冷了
mommy oh that's because I've got cold
now please open the door oh oh
哦,妈妈哦,那是因为我已经冷了 现在请打开门哦哦哦哦
现在请开门哦哦哦哦哦
now please open the door oh oh
no come on in
现在请打开门 哦 哦 哦 不进来吧
不进来吧
no come on in
mommy I'll get some water for
不,进来妈妈,我去拿些水
you here you
你在这里,你在这里,你在这里
are you're not
# 你是否不是 # # # 你是否不是 # # # 你是否不是 # # # 是否不是 # # # 你不是 # # # # 你不是 # # # # # # # # # 你不是 # # # # # 你不是 # # # # # # # # 你不是 # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # #
mommy
你不是妈妈吗?
妈妈
mommy
of course I'm
我当然是妈妈
当然,我
of course I'm
not you have nowhere to
当然我不是你无处可去
你无处无处可去
not you have nowhere to
run what a sneaky wolf where is he
你无处可逃 何等鬼鬼鬼祟祟的狼在哪里
跑什么鬼鬼鬼祟祟的狼 他在哪里
run what a sneaky wolf where is he
hiding
跑什么鬼鬼鬼鬼祟祟的狼 躲到哪里去了
隐藏
hiding
now huh it's Wolf's
现在藏起来啊,是狼的
clothes he must be somewhere around here
衣服一定在附近
he always disguises himself as others to
他衣服一定在附近 他总是伪装成其他人
他总是把自己伪装成别人
he always disguises himself as others to
get children to open the
他总是把自己伪装成其他人 让孩子打开
让儿童打开
get children to open the
door hi there this is Sheriff
让孩子们打开门 嗨,这是警长
你好,我是警长
door hi there this is Sheriff
Labrador have you seen this person
你好,我是拉布拉多警长 你见过这个人吗?
拉布拉多,你见过这个人吗?
Labrador have you seen this person
around
拉布拉多,你见过这个人吗?
周围
around
here let's go to the rabbit's house and
我们到兔子家去
ask they're coming I need to get changed
我们到兔子家去 问他们要来 我要换衣服
问他们来了,我要换衣服
ask they're coming I need to get changed
hello anybody
问他们来了,我需要换换衣服
大家好,大家好
hello anybody
there may I help you miss rabbit have
有人在吗? 我可以帮你想念兔子吗?
我可以帮你想念兔子吗?
there may I help you miss rabbit have
you seen this person around here oh h no
我能帮你想念兔子吗? 你见过这个人吗?
你在这附近见过这个人吗? 哦,不
you seen this person around here oh h no
I haven't I'm not feeling well today so
你在这附近见过这个人 哦,不,我今天不觉得不舒服,所以...
我今天身体不舒服,所以...
I haven't I'm not feeling well today so
I stayed home all day uh Miss Rabbit why
我今天不舒服,所以我整天呆在家里... 兔子小姐,为什么?
我整天在家 兔子小姐 为什么
I stayed home all day uh Miss Rabbit why
is your leg gray it's it's the latest
我整天在家 兔子小姐 为何你的腿是灰色的 这是最新的
是你的腿灰色 这是最新的
is your leg gray it's it's the latest
fashion and what about your face it's
你的腿是灰色的 你的腿是灰色的 这是最新的时尚
时时时时时,你的脸容
fashion and what about your face it's
gray too I think I got some ashes on my
时时时时时时,你的脸脸也灰灰了 我想我身上有些灰灰
灰灰灰灰的,我觉得我身上有些灰灰
gray too I think I got some ashes on my
face while cleaning the
灰灰灰灰的,我还想我脸上有灰灰 在打扫的时候
清扫脸部时清洗脸部
face while cleaning the
chimney excuse me I need to rest now
清扫烟囱时要当面洗脸,不好意思,我现在需要休息了
烟囱,对不起,我需要休息了
chimney excuse me I need to rest now
wait you're not Miss
烟囱,对不起,我需要休息 现在等待你不是小姐
等等,你不是小姐
wait you're not Miss
Rabbit you're
你是兔子吗?
wolf see you later stop Sheriff
狼狼回头见 警长,站住
Labrador
狼狼再见了 拉布拉多警长
拉布拉多
Labrador
stop right
拉布拉多向右停
there
此处
what
什么什么是
ouch now watch
现在看什么看
this
这笔
bye-bye
再见
you will never catch
永别了,你永远抓不到
me you can't run
你跑不了我,你跑不了
away nobody can run away from
无人能逃避
me Sheriff labrador's safety
我是拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids when you're home alone never
独独在家的时候跟孩子聊天 从来不会
open the door to anyone except your
当你独自在家的时候 和孩子聊天 永远不要向任何人敞开大门 除了你
向除你以外的任何人敞开大门
open the door to anyone except your
parents bad guys might use sneaky ways
向任何人敞开大门 除了你父母 坏人可能会用鬼鬼鬼祟祟的方式
做父母的坏人 可能会用鬼鬼鬼鬼祟祟的方式
parents bad guys might use sneaky ways
to fool you and trick you into opening
做父母的坏人 可能会用鬼鬼鬼祟祟的方式 骗骗你 骗你开张
骗骗你,骗你开
to fool you and trick you into opening
the door please don't fall for them call
骗你,骗你,骗你开门 请不要被他们迷上
门门,请不要被他们迷上
the door please don't fall for them call
your parents right away if there are
门门请不要被他们迷上 如果有的话 立刻打电话给你父母
如果有的话,请立刻将您的父母通知您的父母
your parents right away if there are
strangers at your door
如果你家门口有陌生人 就马上去你父母家
陌生人在你的门前
strangers at your door
remember what we've learned today
在你门口的陌生人 记得我们今天学到的东西
记住我们今天学到的东西
remember what we've learned today
left train
记得我们今天学到的 离开火车的教训
safety Come on Mommy let's go the
安全,来吧,妈妈,让我们去
Train's leaving soon all passengers
安全安全,妈妈,我们上火车,所有乘客都马上离开
火车马上就要开走了 所有乘客
Train's leaving soon all passengers
please get on
火车马上就要出发了 所有乘客请上车
请上船吧
please get on
board Doby what's this big suitcase for
多比,请上船,这个大箱子干什么?
Doby 这个大手提箱是用来干什么的?
board Doby what's this big suitcase for
a long trip like this of course I'm
多比板上,什么是这个大手提箱 长途旅行,像这样,我当然是
这么长的旅程 我当然是
a long trip like this of course I'm
bringing CL some
这么长的旅程 我当然要带些CL
带一些 CL 来
bringing CL some
things oh wow automatic doors h
带来一些东西哦哇自动门啊
amazing JY are you okay I'm so sorry
令人惊叹的杰Y,你没事吧 对不起,对不起
sweetie stop running
令人惊叹的JY,你没事吧 对不起,亲爱的 停止跑跑
甜心停止运行
sweetie stop running
around the Train's leaving soon have a
小甜甜别在火车上跑跑 很快就要出发了
火车要出发了 很快就要有一个了
around the Train's leaving soon have a
pleasant
火车马上要出发了 旅途愉快
舒适
pleasant
journey
旅行旅费
y
y y , y
wow it's so
你哇,这是如此
beautiful it's so
如此美丽 如此美丽
hot the Train's arriving soon at
热火车马上就要到了
rainforest station please prepare to get
火车马上就要到雨林站了 请准备好
雨林站请准备
rainforest station please prepare to get
off it stopped I can get off and play wo
雨林站,请准备下车 停下,我可以下车 和玩WO
停止了,我可以下车 和玩WO
off it stopped I can get off and play wo
cake cake cake I made
我停了下来,我可以下车 和玩两个蛋糕蛋糕,我做的蛋糕
it what what shall I
我该做什么?
choose this and this I want them
我该选择什么 选择这个和我想要他们
all wait for me
都等着我
train oh little bear where are
训练小熊小熊 在那里
you Miss bear what's
熊小姐,你在哪里? 熊小姐,什么?
小姐,你怀着什么
you Miss bear what's
wrong Sheriff Labrador my child was
你怀着什么是错的 警长拉布拉多
拉布拉多警长错了 我的孩子
wrong Sheriff Labrador my child was
running around on the train and now he's
错误的拉布拉多警长 我的孩子在火车上跑来跑去
跑在火车上,现在他
running around on the train and now he's
missing what should I do don't worry
在火车上跑来跑去 现在他失踪了 我该担心什么
少了什么我应该做什么 不要担心
missing what should I do don't worry
Miss bear we'll help you find Little
我会帮你找到小小
小熊小姐,我们帮你找小熊
Miss bear we'll help you find Little
Bear
熊小姐 我们会帮你找到小熊
熊熊
Bear
what should I do the Train's
忍着点,我该做什么? 火车的
我该做什么? 火车的
what should I do the Train's
gone
我该做什么? 火车车走了?
已 远
gone
mommy hey kid looking for your
妈妈 来找你的小孩
妈妈,嘿,孩子在找你
mommy hey kid looking for your
mommy come with me I'll help you find
找妈妈的小孩 跟我走 我来帮你找
妈妈跟我来,我帮你找
mommy come with me I'll help you find
your mommy really thank you
妈妈跟我来 我会帮你找到你妈妈 真的谢谢你
你妈妈真的非常感谢你
your mommy really thank you
sir he fell for
你妈妈真的非常感谢您 先生,他爱上了
it sir I want to have some cake do we
先生,我想吃点蛋糕
find your mommy but I'm so hungry please
先生,我想吃点蛋糕 我们能不能找到你的妈妈 但我好饿,求你了
去找你妈妈,但我好饿,拜托
find your mommy but I'm so hungry please
all right all right I'll buy you one
去找你妈妈,但我肚子好饿,求你了 好,我给你买一个
W come on have some then let's go find
来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来来,我们去找找找
your
来,来,吃点,我们去找你
贵国的
your
mom have you seen this kid around no
你妈妈见过这个孩子吗?
妈妈,你有没有见过这个孩子?
mom have you seen this kid around no
have you seen this kid no I haven't uhuh
妈妈你见过这个孩子吗? 你见过这个孩子吗?
你见过这个孩子吗?
have you seen this kid no I haven't uhuh
oh miss rabbit have you seen Little Bear
你见过这个孩子吗? 没有,我还没有 uhuhoh哦 兔子小姐 你有没有见过小熊
兔子小姐,你见过小熊吗?
oh miss rabbit have you seen Little Bear
around oh he's the one who was running
哦,兔子小姐 你有没有看到小熊在周围 哦,他是一个谁在奔跑
在Oh周围,他是一个 谁在奔跑
around oh he's the one who was running
around on the train and he knocked over
他就是那个在火车上跑来跑去的 撞倒了
在火车上,他撞倒了
around on the train and he knocked over
my plate he went that
在火车上,他撞翻了我的盘子
我的盘子,他走了
my plate he went that
way I'm so sorry Miss
我的盘子,他往那边去了 对不起,小姐
对不起,小姐
way I'm so sorry Miss
Rabbit Mr
对不起,兔子小姐先生
兔子先生
Rabbit Mr
slot have you seen Little
小兔先生,你见过小兔先生吗?
你见过小小小
slot have you seen Little
Bear yes great where is he he just got
你见过小熊吗? 他在哪里?
记住,他刚到哪里去了?
Bear yes great where is he he just got
off the train oh no he's at ring Forest
他刚从火车上下到哪里? 哦,不,他在森林环
下火车 哦不不,他在环森林
off the train oh no he's at ring Forest
Station we need to take the train
不不 他在林林车站 我们要坐火车
back sir I want some more I want some
先生,我还想要一些,我要一些
more
先生,我要再来一点,我要再来一点
why are you eating so much come with me
为何你吃这么多东西 跟我来
right
为什么你吃这么多东西 跟我一起来
右右右右右
right
now I don't want to go with you I'm
我现在不想和你一起去
going to fight Bonnie don't even think
现在我不想和你一起去 我要和Bonnie决斗 想都别想
想都别想 {\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF\3cH
going to fight Bonnie don't even think
about it leave him
和Bonnie决斗 想都别想 离开他
任随他去吧!
about it leave him
alone oh no the police
离他远一点 哦,没有警察
没有警察
alone oh no the police
mommy sweetie mommy was so worried I
哦,没有警察 妈妈妈妈亲爱的妈妈 如此担心我
妈妈宝贝妈妈很担心我
mommy sweetie mommy was so worried I
won't run around
妈妈宝贝妈妈很担心我不会到处跑
again
再次再次
stop
再次停止
oh
哦
no over
无以上
there don't push don't
不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
push Sheriff
推推警长
labador Make Way for us
推推警长拉巴道尔·拉巴多 为我们让路
please stop right there oh
请你站住,站住,哦
no
请你站住,哦,不,哦,不
无 无
no
stop why won't they stop chasing me aha
他们为什么不停止追我?
为什么他们不停止追我?
stop why won't they stop chasing me aha
I got to run through
为什么他们不停止追我,为什么他们不停止追我? 啊哈,我必须跑过去
我得跑过去
I got to run through
there don't step over the safety line
我要穿过那里,不要跨过安全线
在那里不要跨过安全线
there don't step over the safety line
I'm not listening to
不要跨过安全线 我听不到
我没在听
I'm not listening to
you
我没在听你说话
您 您 的 您 您
you
a watch
你们只表表表一表,
me that was close that's so
那时我离我很近
scary Sheriff labor safety
可怕的劳动安全警长
talk kids when you take the train please
你坐火车的时候跟小孩说话,拜托了
be
当你坐火车的时候 和孩子聊天,请
be be be 的, 是
be
careful when you're on the platform
在月台上要小心一点
当你在平台上时小心小心
careful when you're on the platform
don't step over the safety line you
当你在平台上时小心小心 不要跨过安全线
不要跨过安全线
don't step over the safety line you
might fall or get caught under the train
不要跨过安全线 你可能会跌倒或被火车抓住
可能跌落或被困在火车下
might fall or get caught under the train
watch your step and wait in line when
可能摔倒或被困在火车下 看着你的脚步 排队等待
注意脚步,排队等候
watch your step and wait in line when
getting on and off the train don't push
小心脚步,排队等候 上下火车时不要推
上下火车不要推
getting on and off the train don't push
others and stay close to your
上下火车,别推别人 离你近一点
和你们所亲近的人,
others and stay close to your
parents and never run around or get off
其他人跟紧你父母 千万别跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑
父母从不跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑
parents and never run around or get off
the train alone please remember
父母从不跑来跑来跑去 也从来不一个人下车 请记住
that scary Dino
可怕的迪诺
robot
机器人机器人
wow it's so
哇,这是如此
cool do you like it little kid uh-huh I
哇,太酷了,你喜欢它 小孩 嗯,嗯,我
酷,你喜欢它 小孩 嗯,嗯,我
cool do you like it little kid uh-huh I
do I'll give it to you for free huh for
你喜欢它吗? 喜欢它的孩子 嗯,嗯,我做我会给你免费的,呵呵
我会免费送给你
do I'll give it to you for free huh for
free that's right for free wow thank you
我会免费免费送给你 免费免费的 免费的
免费免费,谢谢
free that's right for free wow thank you
so much goodbye
免费的免费,谢谢,再见了
如此多的道别
so much goodbye
bye good night sweetie good night good
再见 晚安 亲爱的 晚安 晚安
night Mommy and
晚安 亲爱的晚安 晚安妈妈和
Daddy
爹 爹 爹 爸
is it morning
是早晨吗?
T-Rex where are you
T -Rex,你在哪里? 你在哪里?
going
继续
mommy
妈妈
daddy where is our
妈妈爸爸,我们在哪里?
son
子孙
Sheri Labrador we were asleep and
谢里拉布拉多 我们睡着了
suddenly woke up to the sound of a
Sheri Labrador 我们睡着了 突然醒来
突然醒来
suddenly woke up to the sound of a
scream and our son was
突然醒来 听到尖叫声 我们的儿子
我们的儿子尖叫着
scream and our son was
missing please have us don't worry
我们的儿子失踪了 请不要担心
请让我们不要担心
missing please have us don't worry
there's no case that I can't
请让我们不要担心 没有案子我办不到
没有什么案子我不能办
there's no case that I can't
solve
解答
ouch who bit my bottom that
谁咬我的底部
hurts the T-Rex look so
谁咬我的屁股 伤害T -Rex看起来如此
伤T -Rex的外观如此
hurts the T-Rex look so
scary we got it from a strange young
我们从一个陌生的年轻人那里得到的 我们从一个奇怪的年轻人那里得到的
我们从一个奇怪的年轻人那里得到的恐怖
scary we got it from a strange young
lady for
我们从一个奇怪的年轻女士那里得到的
女 女 女 女 女 女 女 女 女 女
lady for
free
免费女性
oh there must be something wrong with
一定有什么不对劲
the T-Rex papion check it right now got
哦,一定有什么问题 与T -Rex papion检查 它现在得到了
T -Rex papion 检查它现在得到的
the T-Rex papion check it right now got
it
其 其 年 , 其 年 , 其 年 , 其
here's the result there's a remote
结果是有遥控器
control chip inside the
结果是 里面有一个遥控芯片
内部控制芯片
control chip inside the
T-Rex looks like a bad person lured away
T -Rex内部的控制芯片 看起来像一个坏人被诱走
T -Rex看起来像一个坏人 被诱走了
T-Rex looks like a bad person lured away
little bison by a remote control
T -Rex看起来像一个坏人 被遥控器诱走的小野牛
遥控的小野牛
little bison by a remote control
T-Rex but what should we
遥控的小野牛 T -雷克斯 但是我们应该怎样
do I've already located their
我已经找到他们了
position let's go save little
我已经找到他们的位置了 省点钱吧
位置,让我们去节省一点
position let's go save little
bison
牛 牛
I want to go
我想走,我想离开
home I can't stand it
我想回家,我受不了
anymore it's little bison's voice
已经是小野牛的声音了
hurry hey
已经是小野牛的声音了,快点
stop how do they find me
他们如何停止找到我
here what do I
他们怎么在这里找到我?
我在这里做什么?
here what do I
do I have a
我在这里做什么? 我有一个
我有一个
do I have a
plan
计划计划
watch
观察观察
me take a look at
我看看,我看一看
this
这笔
it's so
就是这样
slippery aren't my toys
我的玩具不是滑滑的
amazing hey Doby
令人惊叹的嗨,多比 嘿,多比
papum
令人惊叹的嘿嘿,多比帕普姆
coming
即将到来
oh
哦
no Sher laor stop right
绝不停止,不要停在右侧
there heading to the end of the Earth
直向地球尽头
goodbye oh no she escaped again don't
哦,不,不,她又逃出来了,不要
worry I've already hacked into her car
哦,不,不,她再次逃脱 不用担心我已经黑进她的车了
担心我已经黑进她的车了
worry I've already hacked into her car
control
担心我已经侵入她的汽车控制控制系统了
控制控制
control
system let me give her a surprise
让我给她一个惊喜
系统让我给她一个惊喜
system let me give her a surprise
hey you'll never catch Dr
系统让我给她一个惊喜 嘿,你永远抓不到Dr
antel now heading to the police
Antel现在向警察报到
station what's going
Antel现在前往警察局 发生什么了
on oh I failed again Andel you're under
哦,我再次失败 再次失败,安黛尔你下
arrest
哦,我再次失败 再次失败 安黛儿 你被捕了
逮捕和逮捕
arrest
Sheriff labrador's safety
逮捕拉布拉多警长的安全
拉布拉多警长的安全
Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids you shouldn't take anything
和孩子说话,你不应该拿任何东西
from strangers there might be something
你不应该从陌生人那里拿走任何东西 可能有什么东西
从陌生人那里 可能有什么
from strangers there might be something
dangerous in those things so you should
陌生人从陌生人那里来 这些东西可能有危险 所以你应该
那些危险的东西,你应当用它做危险的东西,你应当用它做危险的东西,你应当用它做危险的东西,
dangerous in those things so you should
be careful can you remember that
危险的东西,所以你应该小心。 你还记得吗?
left who's following
离开的随行者
me stop right
我右站右站右站右站右站
there
站住,站住,站住
oh no black mamba got away again we need
哦,没有黑色的曼巴再次逃脱 我们需要
to catch him before he harms other
哦,没有黑色曼巴再次逃脱 我们要在他伤害别人之前抓住他
kids finally got away from the
孩子们终于逃离了
plan
孩子们终于脱离了计划
计划计划
plan
bye
计划拜拜
the kid is alone it's my chance to take
那孩子孤孤孤一人,这是我的机会 抓住机会
her so
所以她这么
yummy what's that sound who is it
好吃,那声音是什么? 是谁?
h Mr Beaver there's something strange in
海狸先生,有些奇怪的东西
that pile of
海狸先生 那堆东西里有奇怪的东西
堆积
that pile of
ropes let me take a
一堆绳子让我拿一捆绳子
look kid this is just a normal rope
小子,这只是一条普通的绳子
look thank you sir you're
先生,谢谢您
welcome where did the Rope
欢迎到哪里去了? 绳子在哪里?
go
上去
H I'm going to catch
我会赶上的
you the strange sound again who's
怪异的声音又响起
following
跟着你那奇怪的声音 跟着你
me Daddy can you teach me to jump rope
爸爸,你能教我跳绳吗?
of course again Daddy
爸爸,你能教我跳绳吗? 爸爸,你能不能教我跳绳?
当然了,爸爸
of course again Daddy
awesome
当然了,爸爸好棒极了
oops the Rope is too slippery son let's
绳子太滑了,儿子,我们走吧
just go play
绳子太滑了,儿子,我们去玩吧
soccer I'm going to catch you this
踢足球,我要抓住你这个
time
时间
sh
sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh
labador the
拉巴多·拉巴多·卡巴多·卡巴多·
police someone's following me what don't
警方有人跟踪我 却不跟踪我
be afraid little rabbit we will keep you
警察有人跟踪我 不用担心小兔子 我们会留你
怕小兔子,我们会留你
be afraid little rabbit we will keep you
safe let's go check it
怕小兔子,我们会保护你的安全 我们去看看
out there's no one
外面没人
here this is the Trail of a
这儿就是...
snake
蛇蛇 蛇蛇蛇
what's
什么是
this this is Black Mamba scale it's
这是什么,这是黑色曼巴比例表
这是黑色曼巴比例表
this this is Black Mamba scale it's
black mamba who's following little
这是黑色的曼巴比例表 是黑色的曼巴
黑色的曼巴,谁的跟随小小
black mamba who's following little
rabbit it's him again this time he won't
跟踪小兔子的黑曼巴黑曼巴 这次他不会了
兔子又来了,这次他不会了
rabbit it's him again this time he won't
get
兔子又来了,这次他又抓不到了
away that's
离远处
it little rabbit we looked around no
是小兔子 我们环顾四周,没有
one's following you don't worry just go
小兔子,我们到处看,没人跟着你 你不用担心,走吧,走吧
the police couldn't find
警方找不到
me I'm going to catch you
警方找不到我 我会抓到你
我,我,我会抓住你
me I'm going to catch you
kid this is a faster way
我要抓到你 小子 这是条更快的路
home a perfect place to catch the
一个完美的地方 捕捉
kid don't run little
小子,别跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑小跑
rabbit
兔子兔子
huh you can't get away I wasn't planning
你逃不掉的,我可没计划
on getting away
你逃不掉的 我本来不打算逃跑的
离开
on getting away
H the
H H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和 H 和
H 和
H the
police we've already seen through your
警方,我们已经看到 通过你
警方,我们已经通过你见过
police we've already seen through your
tricks this is called bluring the
我们通过你的把戏已经看过警察了 这叫模糊
这个把戏叫做模糊
tricks this is called bluring the
snake you've got neon spray paint on you
这个把戏叫做"模糊蛇" 你身上涂有烟雾喷漆
蛇蛇,你身上涂有射线喷漆
snake you've got neon spray paint on you
you can't run away chase
蛇... 蛇... 你身上涂有射线喷漆... 你跑不掉的追追追
him there you are
他在那里,你在那里,你在那里
the paint stopped
涂料停止
here why is there a light
为何有光明
here no that's black mamba they found
为什么这里有光线 没有黑曼巴
这里没有,这是他们找到的黑色曼巴
here no that's black mamba they found
me nobody can run away from
不在这里,这是黑色的曼巴 他们发现我 没有人可以逃离
没有人能逃离我
me nobody can run away from
me sherff labrador's safety
我谢尔夫·拉布拉多的安全
talk kids going out alone can be
一个人出去聊天的孩子 可能是
dangerous if you notice someone
一个人出去聊天的孩子 可能会很危险 如果你注意到某人
如果你注意到某人,危险
dangerous if you notice someone
following you don't panic stay calm and
如果你注意到有人跟踪你 就不会惊慌 保持冷静
跟着你,不要惊慌 保持冷静,
following you don't panic stay calm and
quickly run to a crowded place and ask
跟着你不要惊慌 保持冷静 快速跑到拥挤的地方问
快速跑到拥挤的地方问
quickly run to a crowded place and ask
for
迅速跑到拥挤的地方,要求
用于
for
help please remember these tips
请记住这些提示
帮助您记住这些提示
help please remember these tips
W don't eat dirty
请记住这些小费,不要吃脏东西
food
食品食品
wow Mr Fox I want one you all right just
哇 福克斯先生 我想要一个你没事的
a moment here here here you
福克斯先生,我要一个你没事的,就在这里片刻,你在这里
are what's
是什么是
this
这是什么?
Mr Fox what's this black
福克斯先生 这是什么黑色的
thing
福克斯先生,什么是这个黑色的东西
事项
thing
uh it's just chocolate you seem to
嗯,这只是巧克力 你似乎喜欢
really like my salad I'll give you
只是巧克力 你好像很喜欢我的沙拉 我会给你的
真的很喜欢我的沙拉,我会给你
really like my salad I'll give you
another
真的喜欢我的沙拉,我再给你一份
另一个
another
one
彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此
thanks oh my tummy hurts
谢谢,我的肚子好痛哦
oh where's the
哦,谢谢哦,我的肚子痛哦,哦,哪里
restroom why are there so many people
为什么有这么多人来洗手间?
here ow my told
为什么这里有这么多人 听从我的话
me
我,我,我
uh-oh they don't look well oh my
哦,哦,他们看起来不好看 哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦,哦
dummy Sheriff Labrador all these people
哦,他们看起来不好看 哦,我的假假警长拉布拉多 所有这些人
拉布拉多的假警长 所有这些人
dummy Sheriff Labrador all these people
got food poisoning huh something's
假的拉布拉多警长 这些人都有食物中毒
食物中毒 食物中毒
got food poisoning huh something's
wrong huh food poisoning goby please
食物中毒? 食物中毒? 食物中毒?
食物中毒
wrong huh food poisoning goby please
find out what they ate
请查查他们吃了什么
today hey kid how are you
小子,今天你好吗?
feeling I've got the runs three times
小子,今天你感觉怎么样? 我有三次跑步
感觉我三次跑步
feeling I've got the runs three times
do you remember what you ate
感觉我有三次跑步 你记得你吃了什么吗?
你还记得你所吃的东西吗?
do you remember what you ate
today I had ice cream fruit salad and a
你还记得你今天吃什么吗? 今天我吃了冰淇淋水果沙拉
今天我吃了冰淇淋水果沙拉
today I had ice cream fruit salad and a
cake oh no I need to go
今天我吃了冰淇淋水果沙拉和蛋糕
again sir here's the report they all had
先生,这是他们所有的报告
ice cream cake and fruit
先生,这是报告,他们都有冰淇淋蛋糕和水果
冰淇淋蛋糕和水果
ice cream cake and fruit
salad let's go investigate these
冰淇淋蛋糕和水果沙拉 我们去调查一下
shops it's not me
店铺不是我,不是我
my cake shop has been here for 100 years
店铺不是我,我的蛋糕店 已经在这里100年了
我的蛋糕店在这里已经100年了
my cake shop has been here for 100 years
such a thing has never happened since my
我的蛋糕店已经在这里100年了 自从我
从我出生到现在 从未发生过这样的事
such a thing has never happened since my
grandfather's grandfather was
自从我祖父的祖父出生后 从未发生过这样的事
祖父的祖父曾是
grandfather's grandfather was
here not me I'm sure that nothing's
不是我在这里,我敢肯定,没有什么
wrong with my yummy ice
这里不是我,我敢肯定 我的美味冰没有问题
cream look my ice cream's
看看我的冰淇淋
fine what are you suspecting me my shop
你怀疑我的店铺?
is really clean every fruit salad is
你怀疑我什么都行 我的店里每一份水果沙拉都干净
每一个水果沙拉都是干净的
is really clean every fruit salad is
carefully selected by
每一个水果沙拉都是由
仔细选择的
carefully selected by
myself I'm prepared by
由我亲自准备
myself wow I love fruit salad I'd like
哇,我喜欢水果沙拉,我喜欢
to have one please great
哇,我爱水果沙拉 我想有一个请大方的
choice I don't think there is any
我不认为有选择
problem with those shops
我不认为那些商店有什么问题
与这些商店有问题
problem with those shops
don't eat
那些商店不吃东西的问题
不吃不吃
don't eat
it I smelled rotten fruit in Mr Fox's
别吃,我闻到福克斯先生家的腐烂水果味
我在福克斯先生家闻到了腐烂水果的味道
it I smelled rotten fruit in Mr Fox's
salad shop he must be hiding
我在福克斯先生的沙拉店里闻到了腐烂水果的味道 他一定藏起来了
沙拉店,他一定躲在沙拉店里
salad shop he must be hiding
something what isn't that Mr Fox what is
沙拉店 他一定在隐瞒什么 不是福克斯先生
福克斯先生不是那样的人
something what isn't that Mr Fox what is
he doing
福克斯先生在做什么? 他在做什么?
there let's go follow
在那里,我们跟着走
him
世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世
rotting fruit is
腐烂的果实是
everywhere those police officers
到处都是那些警察
believed what I
到处都是那些警官 都相信我所相信的
信仰我所信仰的
believed what I
said huh huh I don't care about rotten
信我所说的话吧? 我才不在乎腐烂
说哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈(我不关心腐烂烂烂烂烂烂烂烂烂烂的烂的烂
said huh huh I don't care about rotten
fruit I'm not eating them
说吧,我不在乎 腐烂水果,我不吃
anyway Mr Fox it was you who made people
反正福克斯先生 是你创造了人
sick a
反正福克斯先生 是你让人生病的
生病a
sick a
police come with us to the police
一个生病的警察 跟我们去报警
警察和我们一起去找警察
police come with us to the police
station I I I'm going to
警察和我们一起去警察局 我要到警察局去
车站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站一站
station I I I'm going to
run
运行中
OU see you
再见
later you can have it s
稍后,你可以拥有它S
it's so disgusting huh you don't want to
太恶心了,你不想吗?
eat rotten fruit do you you're so bad
太恶心了 你不想吃腐烂水果吗? 你这么坏吗?
吃腐烂的水果 你这么坏吗?
eat rotten fruit do you you're so bad
you are going to the police station with
吃腐烂的水果 你这么坏,你要去警察局 与
us ow my tummy please take me to the
我肚子疼,请带我去
hospital
我肚子疼,请带我去医院
医院医院
hospital
first sheriff labrador's safety
第一警长拉布拉多的安全
dock kids check your food before eating
码头儿童在吃饭前先检查一下食物
if it looks dirty or rotten or it's past
码头的孩子们在吃之前先检查你的食物,如果它看起来脏或烂,或者已经过去
如果它看起来肮脏或腐烂 或者它已经过去
if it looks dirty or rotten or it's past
its expiration date you shouldn't eat
如果它看起来脏脏或烂,或者已经过期, 你不应该吃
它的过期日期 您不应该吃
its expiration date you shouldn't eat
it rotten food can cause stomach ache
它的到期日,你不应该吃它 腐烂的食物会导致胃痛
腐烂的食物会胃痛
it rotten food can cause stomach ache
and even food poisoning please keep
腐烂的食物会导致胃痛 甚至食物中毒
连食物中毒都留下
and even food poisoning please keep
these in
连食物中毒 也请保留这些
mind safety in swimming
游泳时的智力安全
pools Mark stop right there you never
在游泳池里安全 马克 在那里停下,你从来没有
马克游泳池停在那里,你从来没有
pools Mark stop right there you never
catch
马克游泳池停在那里,你永远抓不到
hey my
嘿,我的
donuts oh
甜甜甜甜甜甜圈哦
no I need to hide a lot little ducks
不,我需要藏很多小鸭子
under the bridge come along and count
不需要我把很多小鸭子藏在桥下 来数数
桥下,桥下,起而起,数,
under the bridge come along and count
with me 1 2 3 4 5
与我一起数数 12 3 4 5
与我同在 1 2 3 4 5
with me 1 2 3 4 5
a that's
a 系指
it quack
响起,
quack quack
孔拳
quack he got away again hi officer
他又逃走了,警官,你好
hi huh is
嗨,哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
that Thief chicken's prison uniform oh
哈哈哈哈哈哈是盗贼鸡的监狱制服哦
那个盗贼鸡的监狱制服哦
that Thief chicken's prison uniform oh
no looks like he's hiding among the
那条小偷鸡的监狱制服 哦,没有看起来像他躲在
没有看起来他躲在
no looks like he's hiding among the
Ducks let's go
他好像躲在鸭子中间,我们走吧
now huh they all look
现在,他们现在都看看
alike huh I got to go find him wait if
现在他们看起来都长得都一样吗? 我得去找他等
我一定要去找他等,如果
alike huh I got to go find him wait if
you surprise him he might hurt the Ducks
我要去找他 如果你给他惊喜,他可能会伤到鸭子
你给他惊喜 他可能会伤到鸭子
you surprise him he might hurt the Ducks
around him H I have an
你给他惊喜 他可能会伤到周围的鸭子
idea we're the new swimming coaches
认为我们是新来的游泳教练
let's start the lesson
说我们是新游泳教练 我们开始上课吧
开始上课吧
let's start the lesson
now huh okay let's do it CRA do you
让我们开始上课吧 好了,让我们开始吧
好了,现在好了,让我们开始吧 来吧,CRA你呢
now huh okay let's do it CRA do you
think we can find him if we disguise his
好吧,好吧,让我们开始吧 CRA,你认为我们可以找到他 如果我们伪装他,我们可以找到他
如果我们伪装他 就会想能找到他
think we can find him if we disguise his
swimming coaches chickens can't swim so
如果我们伪装他的游泳教练 鸡不会游泳,我们就能找到他
游泳教练 鸡不能游泳,所以
swimming coaches chickens can't swim so
we'll be able to find him if we watch
游泳教练 鸡不会游泳 所以我们可以找到他,如果我们看
看着我们就能找到他了
we'll be able to find him if we watch
carefully mhm h
如果我们仔细看,我们就能找到他
ouch that hurts kids this is the first
伤害孩子的触摸 这是第一个
lesson we're going to learn today you
伤害孩子的触摸 这是我们今天要学的第一堂课
我们今天要学到的教训
lesson we're going to learn today you
shouldn't throw things around near the
我们今天要学到的教训 你不应该把东西扔在
不应该把东西扔在附近
shouldn't throw things around near the
pool you might slip and fall put your
不应该把东西扔在游泳池附近 你可能会滑倒摔倒
游泳池可能会滑落 跌落 放下
pool you might slip and fall put your
gear on this shelf yes sir qu and
你可能会滑落和跌倒 把你的装备放在这个架子上 是的,先生
装在这架子上的装备... 是的,先生
gear on this shelf yes sir qu and
remember you must warm up before going
在这架子上的装备 是的 先生 请记住在出发前要热热身才行
记得在去之前必须热热身才能走
remember you must warm up before going
into the pool otherwise you might get
记得在进入游泳池之前必须先热热身才能进游泳池,否则你可能会得到
进入游泳池,否则你可能会得到
into the pool otherwise you might get
muscle cramps everyone follow me let's
否则你可能会肌肉抽筋 所有人都跟着我
大家跟着我,用力抽筋,大家跟着我
muscle cramps everyone follow me let's
warm up okay 1 2 3 4 the police are gone
大家跟着我 暖暖暖一下 12 3 4 警察走了
12 3 4,警察已经走了
warm up okay 1 2 3 4 the police are gone
so no need to hide anymore I got to go 1
12 3 4 警察已经走了 所以不用再躲了 我得去一号了
所以不用再躲藏了 我得去1号了
so no need to hide anymore I got to go 1
2 3 4 1 2 3
所以不需要再躲藏了 我得去12 3 4 4 12 3
2 3 3 4 4 1 2 3
2 3 4 1 2 3
4 oh no it's the
2,3,4,4,1,2,3,4 哦,不,这是
police 1 2 3
警 警 警 警 1 2 3
4 what should I do did they notice
4 我该怎么办 他们注意到了
me
我,我,我
the warm up is done now put on your
我热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热的热热热热热热热热的热热热热热热的热热热热热热热热热热热热的热热热热的热热热热热热的热热热热热热的热热热热的热热热热的热热热用用上你的
热暖化好了 穿上衣服吧
the warm up is done now put on your
safety gear and get ready to swim okay
热暖化完成 穿上安全装备 准备游泳
安全装备,准备游泳
safety gear and get ready to swim okay
quack quack quack let's go
安全装备和准备游泳 好 夸克 夸克 夸克 夸克 我们走
我们走吧 我们走吧
quack quack quack let's go
swimming uhoh I don't know how to swim
游泳啊啊啊啊啊,我不知道怎么游泳
they're going to find me right
我不知道怎么游泳 他们会找到我的
他们会找到我的
they're going to find me right
away what should I do what should I
他们会马上找到我 我该做什么该做什么该做什么
我该做什么该做什么该做什么
away what should I do what should I
do kids let's get into the pool yes sir
我该做什么,我该做什么 孩子们,我们进游泳池吧
孩子们,我们去游泳池吧 是的,长官
do kids let's get into the pool yes sir
quack quack line up and one by one
孩子们,我们到泳池里去吧 是的,先生 夸夸夸的夸夸 排成一排,一个一个一个一个
一个接一个接一个地排成一排
quack quack line up and one by one
squish Splash in the water 1 2 3 4 5
在水中一个接一个接一个 12 3 4 5
在水中喷洒 12 2 3 4 5
squish Splash in the water 1 2 3 4 5
qu wait
在水中喷洒 12 3 4 5 qu 等待
qu 等待
qu wait
huh you didn't wear the swim tube
等等,你没穿泳管
你没有穿泳管
huh you didn't wear the swim tube
correctly that's not
你没有正确穿泳管
正确不正确
correctly that's not
safe I got it let me help
这不正确,那不安全,我得到它 让我来帮忙
安全安全,让我来帮忙
safe I got it let me help
you it's okay I'll do it
安全安全,我来帮你,没事的,我来帮你
myself your
亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲亲
foot huh
长脚(公里)
your head it's
脚踏你的头 它的
头部
your head it's
Justin you're Thief
你的头,你是小偷,是贾斯汀,你是小偷
贾斯汀 你是小偷
Justin you're Thief
chicken you found
贾斯汀,你是小偷鸡,你发现
me you can't run
你跑不了我,你跑不了
away be careful around the pool it's
游泳池周围要小心
slippery
滑滑滑
help I'm snuck in the swim
帮助我溜进游泳
to please help
请求帮助
me that was so
那时的我
scary so he is Thief chicken Thief
所以他就是盗鸡贼
chicken you're under arrest you're
吓吓吓他,所以他是小偷鸡 偷盗鸡鸡,你被捕 你被捕了,你是
鸡鸡你被捕了 你被捕了
chicken you're under arrest you're
coming with us
鸡鸡被捕了 跟我们走
和我们一起走
coming with us
see you shouldn't act like him follow
和我们一起来看看你不该像他一样跟着我们
看你不该像他一样跟着他走
see you shouldn't act like him follow
the safety rules in the swimming pool we
你不应该像他一样 遵守游泳池的安全规则
我们游泳池的安全规则
the safety rules in the swimming pool we
got
我们的游泳池安全规则
已经拥有
got
it Sheriff labrador's safety
是拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids the floor around the pool can
让孩子们在游泳池周围的地板上聊天
be slippery so if you run or throw
说孩子们在游泳池周围的地板上说闲话 游泳池周围的地板很滑 所以如果你跑或扔
滑滑的,如果你们奔跑,或抛掷,
be slippery so if you run or throw
things around near the pool you might
滑滑,所以如果你运行或扔东西 周围的游泳池附近,你可能会
环绕在游泳池周围的东西 你可能会
things around near the pool you might
slip and get
游泳池周围的东西 你可能会滑倒,然后得到
单单,然后获得
slip and get
hurt before swimming you need to warm up
游泳前受伤需要热身
and wear proper safety gear and it's
游泳前需要先热热身 穿适当的安全装备
并穿戴适当的安全装备,它
and wear proper safety gear and it's
dangerous to play in the deep water area
穿着适当的安全装备 在深水区玩很危险
在深水区发生危险
dangerous to play in the deep water area
so play in the kids area only
在深水区玩很危险 所以只在孩子区玩
left little mole is
左左小摩尔是
missing sweetie these fruits are good
亲爱的,这些水果很好吃
for your
少了甜甜,这些水果对你有好处
eyes are you using your tablet again
你的眼睛又在用平板电脑吗?
you're already shortsighted no more
你的眼睛是不是又在用平板电脑了 你已经是短视了
你已经是短视了
you're already shortsighted no more
tablets
你已经是短视了,没有药片了
平板块
tablets
okay let's go
好,我们走吧
please
请
stop sweetie where did he go Little M
小M小M,他去哪儿了? 小M到哪儿去了?
Little
小Mlittle 小Mlittle 他去哪儿了? 小Mlittle 小Mlittle
M my
我的MM
glasses they're
我的眼镜
broken
缺 数
mommy he's my
破碎的妈妈 他是我的
妈妈,他是我的
mommy he's my
daddy where's your mommy
妈妈 他是我爸爸 你妈妈在哪
爸爸,你的妈妈在哪?
daddy where's your mommy
kid
爸爸,你的妈妈孩子在哪?
儿童 儿童
kid
Mommy it's Mommy
妈妈,是妈妈,妈妈
mommy
妈妈
wait
等待等待
Little M Mo what's going on Sheriff
小莫小莫 发生什么事了 警长
Labrador my child is
小莫莫 发生什么事了 拉布拉多警长 我的孩子
拉布拉多 拉布拉多 我的孩子
Labrador my child is
missing little more I saw him getting on
拉布拉多 我的孩子失踪了 我看见他上路了
我看见他上路了
missing little more I saw him getting on
the bus just now oh my goodness
我看见他坐上公交车
刚才的公交车 哦我的天啊
the bus just now oh my goodness
let's go find
刚才的公交车 哦我的天啊,我们去找找
him
世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世
mommy this is the last stop Forest
妈妈,这里是森林最后的一站
Harbor
港端
mommy mommy
港妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈
mommy ice cream mommy are you going to
妈妈 冰淇淋妈妈 你要去
buy me some ice cream what are you
妈妈 冰淇淋 妈妈 你要给我买冰淇淋吗?
买冰淇淋给我吃 你是什么
buy me some ice cream what are you
talking about this is a
买冰淇淋给我买点冰淇淋 你在说什么 这是
说到这个,这是
talking about this is a
bathroom
谈论这是一个厕所
bathroom you're not mommy oh my tummy
洗手间 你不是妈妈 哦我的肚子
ho oh it's stinks
呵哦,它的臭味
uh mommy where are you oh I need to
哦,这是臭的嗯 妈妈,嗯 妈妈在哪里你 哦,哦,我需要
妈妈,你在哪里? 哦,我需要
uh mommy where are you oh I need to
go little mo he's not here not here
小小家伙,他不在这里,不在这里
either are you all right Mr Raccoon have
莱孔先生
you seen little mo little mole he headed
莱孔先生,你有没有看到小摩尔摩
你看见小小摩尔人 他朝他去了
you seen little mo little mole he headed
to the harbor oh no he might be in
你看见小小内鬼了 他朝港口去了 哦,不,他可能在
港湾 哦,不,他也许在
to the harbor oh no he might be in
Danger let's
哦,不,他可能在危险中,让我们
危险,让我们
Danger let's
go
危险,我们走吧
mommy where are
妈妈在哪里
you mommy
妈妈你在哪里 妈妈
mommy no don't close doors are closing
妈妈不要关门,妈妈不要关门,妈妈要关门了
air conditioner I'm so
妈妈不不不关门 妈妈不不关门 关上空调
空调机,我好
air conditioner I'm so
cold little let's split up here
空调机,我好冷,我们分开吧
寒冷的小家伙 我们分开吧
cold little let's split up here
little mo little
寒冷的小家伙,让我们分开在这里 一点点一点一点一点
微微的微小
little mo little
mo little mo help somebody help me huh
帮帮忙 谁来帮我啊
来人帮帮我啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊
mo little mo help somebody help me huh
over
来人帮帮我啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊 来人啊
there look at that it's a little B's bag
看那里,这是个小B的包包
let's
看那里,这是个小B的包包,我们走吧
go I'm am so cold oh no the ship's
走了 我好冷哦,没有船的
leaving hurry
我太冷了,我走了 船没有快离开
赶快离开
leaving hurry
that's it
就是这样
Doby
多比
hey we need to hurry throw me
嘿,我们得快点把我扔出去
over
嘿,我们得快点把我扔过去
okay little more
还可以再多一点
off Doby I'm Sheriff
离开多比,我是警长
Labrador Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多郡长拉布拉多的安全
talk kids your eyes are very important
拉布拉多郡长拉布拉多的安全谈话 你的眼睛非常重要
和孩子说话 你的眼睛很重要
talk kids your eyes are very important
never look at electronic devices for a
你的眼睛非常重要 永远不要看电子设备
从未看过电子设备
never look at electronic devices for a
long time and don't read or write under
很久从不看电子设备,也不读写
长长的时间,不阅读或写作
long time and don't read or write under
dim
长长的时间, 不要在暗暗下读写
暗暗暗
dim
light also don't rub your eyes with
暗光也用不着擦擦眼睛
也不要用光擦擦眼睛
light also don't rub your eyes with
dirty hands it might hurt your
光也不要用肮脏的手摸你的眼睛 那样会伤害你
脏脏脏的手 可能会伤到你
dirty hands it might hurt your
eyes please keep your eyes healthy by
脏手脏手脏手脏 眼睛可能受伤 请保持眼睛健康
请保持双眼健康
eyes please keep your eyes healthy by
practicing these tips every
眼睛请保持健康 每天练习这些小费
每天练习这些提示
practicing these tips every
day the shoe biting
每天,鞋子被咬
escalator
扶梯
oh oh kids be
哦,孩子们哦
careful
仔细小心
look kids where are
看着孩子,看孩子在哪里
you it smells so
你闻起来好臭
good
你闻起来真好闻
良好
good
ouch
好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好, 好
触摸( A)
ouch
oh I'm so sorry I didn't mean it are you
哦,对不起,我不是那个意思 是你
all right Miss squirrel are you in a
哦,对不起,我不是那个意思 你没事 松松小姐是你在
好吧,松松松小姐,你是在
all right Miss squirrel are you in a
rush oh sheriff Labrador my children are
松鼠小姐,你是在赶时间哦 拉布拉多警长 我的孩子
拉布拉多警长 我的孩子们
rush oh sheriff Labrador my children are
missing please help me find them we're
拉布拉多警长 我的孩子们失踪了 请帮我找到他们
请帮我找到他们 我们失踪了
missing please help me find them we're
on
请帮我找到他们
上 年 月
on
it excuse me have you seen two little
恕我失陪了,你看见两只小的,
squirrels around about this tall h
对不起,你见过两只小松鼠吗? 附近有只这么高的松鼠吗?
松鼠周围的松鼠 大约这么高 h
squirrels around about this tall h
I just saw them at the
松鼠周围 大约这个高高的h 我刚刚看到他们在
我刚刚看到他们
I just saw them at the
aquarium thank you
我刚在水族馆看到他们 谢谢
Doby let's split up
多比,我们分开吧
here little squirrels little squirrels
多比,我们分开吧 小松鼠小松鼠小松鼠
小松鼠在这里 小松鼠在这里 小松鼠
here little squirrels little squirrels
little
这里的小松鼠小松鼠小
小
little
squirrels little
小松鼠小
squirrels
松松鼠
aha I found
我发现
you wrong
你错了
person
人 人 人 人
oh no my
哦,不,不,我的
paintings thank goodness they're all
感谢上帝的绘画,他们全都是
safe oh this painting what do you think
谢天谢地,他们都是安全的 哦,这幅画,你觉得怎么样?
这幅画,你觉得呢?
safe oh this painting what do you think
nice H wow are these two monsters
哦,这幅画安全了,你觉得这幅画怎么样? 你觉得这幅画好看吗? 哇,是这两个怪兽
这两只怪兽好哇哇
nice H wow are these two monsters
fighting under a waterfall
这两个怪物在瀑布下战斗
在瀑瀑下战斗
fighting under a waterfall
no
无 无
oh these are two little squirrels on an
哦,这是两只小松鼠
escalator
哦,这是两个小松鼠 在扶梯上
扶梯
escalator
that's right you have good eyes they
扶梯,没错,你有 良好的眼睛,他们
没错,你的眼睛很好看
that's right you have good eyes they
should still be there let's
没错,你的眼睛很好看 他们应该还在那里,让我们
仍然应该在那里,让我们
should still be there let's
go there they
他们到那里去
are I
# 我 # 我 # # # # I # # # I # # # # I # # # # I # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # # #
won a my shoe is
我赢了我的鞋是
stuck watch
挂起手表( 挂起手表)
out
外出
sweetie thank you Sheriff
亲爱的,谢谢你,警长
labador kids playing on the escalator is
谢谢你们,警长拉法多 孩子们玩的扶梯是
坐在扶梯上玩拉拉多的小孩
labador kids playing on the escalator is
very dangerous and you could get
坐在扶梯上玩拉拉多的小孩 是非常危险的,你可以得到
十分危险,你可以得到
very dangerous and you could get
hurt I'm sorry we'll never do that
非常危险,你可能会受伤 对不起,我们永远不会这样做
again
再次再次
Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids you should only take an
说话的小孩,你应该只吃
escalator with your
说话的小孩,你应该只 使用一个扶梯 与你的
与您的
escalator with your
parents and never play around while
和父母一起扶扶梯 暂时不玩
父母不以游戏为乐,不以游戏为乐,
parents and never play around while
standing on it in case of an
父母不依父母而游戏,而当父母与父母在一起的时候,他们不依父母和父母而起立,
遇一种情况时,可以靠它站立,
standing on it in case of an
emergency press the emergency stop
遇有紧急新闻记者 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站 紧急停车站
紧急紧急按紧急停
emergency press the emergency stop
button and the escalator will stop right
按紧急紧急按钮按紧急停止按钮, 扶梯将右停
按钮,自动扶梯将右停
button and the escalator will stop right
away please remember
按钮,自动扶梯将立刻停止,请记住
请记住,请记住
away please remember
that
请记住,请记住
本字幕由AI大模型生成